# RUBENS MENSAH

### WEB DEVELOPER



Abidjan, Riviera golf



07 79 07 42 38



rubs99rstd@gmail.com



https://malickruru.github.io/

# PROGRAMING LANGUAGE

JavaScript PHP

MySQL HTML

CSS TypeScript

### FRAMEWORK/CMS

React.js

Laravel

WordPress

### **SOFTWARE**

Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Access)

Blender

Photoshop

### **LANGUAGE**

French

**English** 

## Resume



PERSONAL PROFILE: I am a front-end specialist web developer. My job is to design solutions for the web, and video games. I am able to carry out a project using the react.js framework, the wordpress CMS or simply in Javascript Vanilla. I also have notions in 3D modeling via Blender software.

### **EDUCATION**

2022 Bachelor in Multimedia Development
Abidjan, Côte d'ivoire Institut Français du Numérique (IFRAN)

2017-2020 Degree in Food Industry

Abidjan, Côte d'ivoire Université Tertiaire et Technologique (UTT) LOKO

2016-2017 Scientific baccalaureate with specialization in biology

Abidjan, Côte d'ivoire LYCEE MAURICE DELAFOSSE

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

09/09/2021 (Abidjan, Côte d'ivoire)

### **7DEVELOP**

Creation of my company (7Develop) which aims to: The creation & distribution of IT solutions (websites, mobile applications, desktop applications, video games, etc.) Link to the official website: https://www.7develop.com

Completed tasks:

- Administrative Management
- IT solution creation

### **7CORTEX**

Du 01/08/2019 au 15/10/2021 (Abidjan, Côte d'ivoire) Position held: Developer

Completed tasks:

- Data base management
- Web page creation
- Maintenance and updating of scripts and existing web applications

#### **CFAO TECHNOLOGIE**

Du 01/04/2015 au 30/04/2015 (Dakar,

Sénégal)

Position held: Internship Completed tasks:

Initiation to computer maintenance work

 $Discover\ my\ work: \underline{\text{https://malickruru.github.io/}}$